SATYA SHIBA MOHAPATRA

Email:satya.mohapatra2014@gmail.com

Mob-9937002641,7008951916

CARRIER OBJECTIVE:

To develop and emerge as a top Ranking Sales & Marketing professional by implementing Innovative ideas, & Action & therefore be recognised as an individual who adds value to Responsibility entrusted and makes a significant contribution to the turn around ,growth& Profitability Of the Organisation,with commitment to excellence and willingness to work hard To achive it.

PROFILE: -20- YEAR EXPERIENCE IN SALES & MARKETING

- Over 20 years of sales experience in sales and marketing, business development including experience in dealer sales and concept selling, Both direct & indirect (Channel)marketing.
- Experience in Business Development withformulation of sales plans strategies and budgets for the achievements of pre-determined targets Posse's strong leadership communication and management's skill.

SALES & MARKETING & BUSINESS DEVLOPMENT

- Evaluate marketing budget periodically including man power planning initiatives and ensure adherence to plan target provide direction to execute the committed objective.
- Conduct competitor's analysis by keeping abreast of market trend and competitors moves to achieve market share.
- Utilize personal network to develop marketing intelligence for generating leads.

WORK EXPERIENCE DETAILS

R R ISPAT LTD (A UNIT OF GODAVARI POWER &ISPAT LTD)

(R R ispat is a Electrical Product manufacturer of HT & LT panels, cable trays, Tower Structure.Angels.Joist etc.)

Worked as Senior Sales Executive (May 2015-Nov-2019)

Job Profile:-

- Responsible for PROJECT-sales & marketing developments covering all over Orissa..
- Cold call & relation building with builders, electrical consultants &govt organisation.
- Visit each and every , commercial & infrastructure construction sites in allotted areas.
- Recruitment & handling sub dealers to generate business
- Responsible for achieving the sales target (monthly / quarterly / annually).
- Get timely feedback from the customers about the product and services.
- Monitor competitor activity.
- Responsible for timly collection of payment & order.
- Prepare sales strategy and identify prospects and convert them into business orders.moe over Fully responsible for the Devlopment of sales & marketing.

JAKSON LIMITED

(A leading GOEM of cumminsindia ltd manufacturer of silent Generator Set 7.5kva-3500kva) Worked as Sales Executive for western odisha(NOV 2012-AUG2014)

Job profile:-

- Responsible for achieving the AOP of Gensets for the territory in terms of sales.
- Responsible for price negotiations discussion rounds with customers (key Decision Makers)
- Responsible for the commercial aspects of sales as well as collection of receivables.
- Developing the distribution channel partners (Dealers and Freelancers) in the territory by providing them sales and technical assistance.
- Key account management Handling key accounts and ensuring that they are satisfied and give continuous business
- Responsible for new lead generation and lead tracking
- Responsible for preparing the product offers to customers
- Implementing promotional activities across the territory.
- Implementation of MIS across the distribution channel.
- Engaging with consultants and contractors to generate business
- Co-ordinating the service support for existing customer base and service teams.
- Generating market and competitor intelligence on a continuous basis

•

SFM, Systematic Fund Management Company

(CO-Operative Society for fund Management)

Worked as Zonal manager(FEB 2010-JUNE 2012)

Job profile:-

- Responsible for revenue generation.
- Responsible to educate sub-ordinate about various investment plans.
- Responsible for MIS and Presentation preparation for management review

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd.

Worked as UNIT Manager, Keonjhar(2006 May-2009 Dec)

Job profile:-

- To plan and achieve business target in the area of number of agents productivity new premium and persistency of business.
- To drive sales promotion effort among advisers & responsible to recruitments of Agent

BENNET PHARMACEUTICALS BARODA

Worked as Area Sales Manager(April 02 - Feb 06)

Job profile:-

- Launch companysNew product range in the entire Western orissa.
- Leads a sales team of 6 person and generating 7lakhs per month.
- Develops new strategies for better penetration.
- Achived a growth leapof 115% in primary sales &160&in secondary sales For the year 02-03.
- Planning and implementing promotional activate,

- Mac laboratories Itd, Mumbai
- Worked as medical representative(May 1993-March2002)
 Job profile:-
 - Responsible for brand promotion, demand generation and to increase the sale volume by generating prescription base.
 - Responsible to achieve sales volume both primary &secondary levels & Dealer satis fiction.
 - Adjudged the star performer for two years
 - 1993-94 Achieved the zonal top by achieving 180%achivement of my Target.
 - 1994-95 Man of Mac award for highest Achievement on all India level & Got Promoted to Field Officer.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION DETAILS

- Matriculation 1985- B S High school Sundergarh
- Intermediate in Commerce -1988-NSCB College ,Sambalpur
- Bachelor of commerce-1991- G.M. College, Sambalpur
- Post Graduate Diploma in Marketing management.

Language Known: Oriya, English, Hindi

STRENGTH

- Highly organized and dedicated with a positive attitude.
- Creative individual with a passion to learn
- Thrive on working in a challenging environment.

CURRENT CTC- 3.24 LAKHS P.A EXCLUDING EXP

PERSONAL DETAILS

Present Contact details

H/O:S.K.NAYAK

At/Po:-Sankarvihar/Gopalmal

Sambalpur(Orissa)

Pin: 768004

Date of Birth: -29.05.1970

I here by declare that the information mentioned above is true and fair to be the Best of my knowledge.

Satya shiba mohapatra